[
    {
        "front": "サッカー",
        "back": "soccer",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "プロ",
        "back": "professional",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんしゅ",
        "back": "athlete",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうらい",
        "back": "future",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆめ",
        "back": "dream",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "ママ",
        "back": "mum",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "パパ",
        "back": "dad",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいじ",
        "back": "important",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "だから",
        "back": "therefore",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "あつまる",
        "back": "to get together; to gather (i.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～を）あつめる",
        "back": "to gather (t.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "よごれる",
        "back": "to become dirty (intr.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～を）よごす",
        "back": "to soil (tr.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "しかる",
        "back": "to scold",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    },
    {
        "front": "わざと",
        "back": "on purpose",
        "chapter": "N4 C19"
    }
]